mazale.in 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Mazale

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

We may collect your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or other personal information from you, however, the information that we collect depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. You can visit many pages on our site without providing any information.

**What information do we collect?**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your Name, Email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

**Children** Children are not allowed on Mazale

**How do we protect visitor information** **?**

  * We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

**We use cookies to:**

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart,
  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits,
  * Keep track of advertisements,

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

It will turn off some of the features of the site

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google** – Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

**We and third party vendors such as Google use:**

To compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Changes to This Policy**  
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Contacting** the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, write to [mazale.com@gmail.com](mailto:mazale.com@gmail.com)
